Guide to the Records of Governor James S. Gilmore, 1998-2002
Library of Virginia
- Series XVIII. Constituent Services: Correspondence (Accession 38938, 39004 and 39776), 1998-2002., Extent: 51.35 cu. ft. (Box 51)
  - Correspondence # 57653-57937, 1999 Feb-Mar. (Box 37, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence # 57940-58119, 1999 Feb-Mar. (Box 38, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence # 58120-58229, 1999 Mar. (Box 38, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence # 58230-58456, 1999 Mar. (Box 38, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence # 58460-58584, 1999 Mar. (Box 38, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence # 58590-58869, 1998 Oct; 1999 Mar-May. (Box 38, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence # 58870-58999, 1998 Oct; 1999 Mar. (Box 38, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence # 59000-59199, 1999 Mar-Apr. (Box 38, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence # 59200-59329, 1999 Mar. (Box 38, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence # 59330-59498, 1999 Mar-Apr. (Box 38, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence # 59500-59629, 1999 Mar. (Box 38, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence # 59630-59779, 1999 Mar-Apr. (Box 38, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence # 59780-59929, 1999 Mar-Apr. (Box 38, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence # 59930-59999, 1999 Mar. (Box 38, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence # 60034-60329, 1999 Mar. (Box 39, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence # 60330-60484, 1999 Mar. (Box 39, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence # 60485-60759, 1999 Mar. (Box 39, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence # 60760-60899, 1999 Mar. (Box 39, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence # 60890-60999, 1999 Mar-Apr. (Box 39, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence # 61000-61100, 1999 Mar. (Box 39, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence # 61111-61198, 1999 Mar. (Box 39, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence # 61200-61319, 1999 Mar. (Box 39, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence # 61320-61418, 1999 Mar. (Box 39, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence # 61420-61549, 1999 Mar. (Box 39, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence # 61550-61689, 1999 Mar-Apr. (Box 39, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence # 61690-61798, 1999 Mar. (Box 39, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence # 61800-62049, 1999 Mar. (Box 39, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence # 62050-62199, 1999 Mar-Apr. (Box 40, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence # 62201-62327, 1999 Mar-Apr. (Box 40, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence # 62330-62468, 1999 Mar-Apr; May. (Box 40, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence # 62470-62599, 1999 Mar-Apr. (Box 40, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence # 62600-62798, 1999 Mar-Apr. (Box 40, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence # 62802-62938, 1999 Mar-Apr. (Box 40, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence # 62940-63089, 1999 Mar-Apr. (Box 40, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence # 63091-63229, 1999 Mar-Apr. (Box 40, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence # 63231-63429, 1999 Mar-Apr; 1998 Sept. (Box 40, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence # 63430-63588, 1999 Mar-Apr. (Box 40, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence # 63590-63759, 1998 Nov; 1999 Mar-Apr. (Box 40, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence # 63760-64028, 1999 Mar-Apr. (Box 40, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence # 64030-64139, 1999 Mar-Apr. (Box 40, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence # 64141-64258, 1999 Mar-Apr. (Box 40, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence # 64260-64395, 1999 Mar-Apr. (Box 41, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence # 64400-64512, 1998 Dec; 1999 Mar-Apr. (Box 41, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence # 64516, 1999 Mar-Apr. (Box 41, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence # 64518-64799, 1999 Mar-Apr. (Box 41, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence # 64800-64997, 1998 Dec; 1999 Mar-Apr. (Box 41, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence # 65002-65229, 1999 Mar-Apr; May. (Box 41, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence # 65230-65359, 1999 Mar-Apr. (Box 41, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence # 65360-65499, 1998 Nov; 1999 Jan; Feb-Apr. (Box 41, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence # 65503-65639, 1999 Jan; Feb-Apr; Sept. (Box 41, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence # 65640-65759, 1999 Feb-Apr. (Box 41, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence # 65760-65989, 1999 Apr; June; Nov (Box 41, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence # 65990-66199, 1998 Nov-Dec; 1999 Apr. (Box 41, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence # 66200-66409, 1999 Apr. (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence # 66410-66537, 1999 Apr-May. (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence # 66540-66689, 1999 Apr-May. (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence # 66690-66869, 1998 Dec; 1999 Apr. (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence # 66870-67039, 1999 Apr. (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence # 67040-67199, 1999 Apr. (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence # 67201-67398, 1999 Apr-May; Aug. (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence # 67400-67526, 1999 Apr-May. (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence # 67530-67679, 1999 Apr-May. (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence # 67680-67829, 1999 Apr-May. (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence # 67830-67999, 1999 Apr-May. (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence # 68000-68191, 1999 Apr-May. (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence # 68210-68449, 1999 Apr-May. (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence # 68450-68715, 1999 Apr-May; Sept. (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence # 68716-68908, 1999 May- June. (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence # 68910-69417, 1999 May-June. (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence # 669150-69459, 1999 May-June. (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence # 69460-69687, 1999 May-June. (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence # 69690-69994, 1999 May-June. (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence # 70006-70258, 1999 May-June. (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence # 70260-70809, 1999 May-June. (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence # 70810-71208, 1999 May-June. (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence # 71210-71644, 1999 May-June. (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence # 71645-71989, 1999 June. (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence # 72009-72429, 1999 June. (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence # 72431-72997, 1999 June. (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence # 73000-73359, 1999 June-Aug. (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence # 73360-73679, 1999 June. (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence # 73680-73939, 1999 June. (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence # 73940-74648, 1999 June-July. (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence # 74650-75298, 1999 June-July. (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence # 75301-75944, 1999 June-July. (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence # 75970-76945, 1999 June-July; Sept. (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence # 76950-77449, 1999 July-Aug. (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence # 77450-77962, 1999 July-Aug. (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence # 77963-78354, 1999 July-Aug. (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence # 78360-78716, 1999 July-Aug. (Box 45, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence # 78720-78974, 1999 July-Aug. (Box 45, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence # 78980-79475, 1999 July-Aug. (Box 45, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence # 79480-80061, 1999 July-Aug. (Box 45, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence # 80070-80499, 1999 Aug. (Box 45, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence # 80500-80578, 1999 Aug. (Box 45, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence # 80588-80999, 1999 Aug-Sept. (Box 45, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence # 81005-81229, 1999 Aug-Sept. (Box 45, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence # 81230-81578, 1999 Aug-Sept. (Box 45, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence # 81580-81897, 1999 Aug-Sept. (Box 45, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence # 81900-82163, 1999 Aug-Sept. (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence # 82165-82539, 1999 Aug-Sept. (Box 45, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence # 82540-82785, 1999 Aug-Sept; Oct. (Box 45, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence # 82790-82999, 1999 Sept. (Box 46, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence # 83007-83239, 1999 Sept. (Box 46, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence # 83240-83513, 1999 Sept. (Box 46, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence # 83520-84089, 1999 Sept-Oct. (Box 46, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence # 84100-84488, 1999 Sept-Oct. (Box 46, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence # 84490-84994, 1999 Sept-Oct. (Box 46, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence # 85001-85419, 1999 Sept-Oct. (Box 46, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence # 85430-85966, 1999 Sept-Oct. (Box 46, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence # 86004-86619, 1999 Sept-Oct. (Box 46, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence # 86620-86844, 1999 Sept-Oct. (Box 46, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence # 86850-87088, 1999 Oct. (Box 46, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence # 87090-87648, 1999 Oct. (Box 46, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence # 87650-88047, 1999 Oct. (Box 46, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence # 88050-88739, 1999 Oct. (Box 47, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence # 88740-89429, 1999 Oct-Nov. (Box 47, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence # 89430-89683, 1999 Oct. (Box 47, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence # 89687-89999, 1999 Oct-Nov. (Box 47, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence # 90000-90389, 1999 Oct-Nov. (Box 47, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence # 90390-90617, 1999 Oct-Nov. (Box 47, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence # 90620-90919, 1999 Oct-Nov. (Box 47, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence # 90920-91495, 1999 Oct-Nov. (Box 47, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence # 91502-91698, 1999 Oct-Nov; Dec. (Box 47, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence # 91702-92049, 1999 Aug; Oct-Nov. (Box 47, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence # 92050-92221, 1999 Aug; Oct-Nov. (Box 47, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence # 92225-92497, 1999 Nov-Dec. (Box 47, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence # 92501-92689, 1999 Nov. (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence # 92690-92799, 1999 Nov. (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence # 92800-92969, 1999 Nov. (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence # 92970-93067, 1999 Nov. (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence # 93070-93375, 1999 Nov. (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence # 93378-93529, 1999 Nov. (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence # 93530-93997, 1999 Nov; Dec. (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence # 94005-94369, 1999 Nov; Dec. (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence # 94370-94988, 1999 Nov; Dec. (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence # 95005-95489, 1999 Nov; Dec. (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence # 95490-95928, 1999 Nov; Dec. (Box 49, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence # 95930-96696, 1999 Nov; Dec. (Box 49, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence # 96700-97149, 1999 Dec. (Box 49, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence # 97150-97480, 1999 Dec. (Box 49, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence # 97481-97696, 1999 Dec. (Box 49, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence # 97702-97869, 1999 Dec. (Box 49, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence # 97870-98379, 1999-2000 Dec; Jan-Feb. (Box 49, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence # 98380-98639, 1999 Dec. (Box 49, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence # 98640-98797, 1999-2000 Dec-Jan. (Box 49, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence # 98802-99081, 1999-2000 Dec; Jan; Feb. (Box 49, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence # 99090-99349, 1999-2000 Dec-Jan. (Box 49, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence # 99350-99488, 2000 Jan. (Box 49, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence # 99490-99719, 2000 Jan. (Box 50, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence # 99720-99899, 2000 Jan; Mar. (Box 50, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence # 99901-100109, 2000 Jan. (Box 50, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence # 100110-100299, 2000 Jan. (Box 50, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence # 100300-100666, 2000 Jan-Feb. (Box 50, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence # 100670-100846, 1999 Dec; 2000 Jan; Feb. (Box 50, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence # 100850-101140, 2000 Jan-Feb. (Box 50, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence # 101150-101436, 2000 Jan-Feb. (Box 50, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence # 101440-101667, 2000 Jan-Feb. (Box 50, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence # 101670-101966, 2000 Jan-Feb. (Box 50, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence # 101970-102389, 2000 Jan-Feb; Mar. (Box 50, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence # 102390-102598, 2000 Feb. (Box 51, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence # 102600-102879, 2000 Feb. (Box 51, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence # 102880-103292, 2000 Feb; Mar. (Box 51, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence # 103303-103517, 2000 Feb. (Box 51, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence # 103520-103859, 2000 Feb. (Box 51, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence # 103860-104169, 2000 Feb. (Box 51, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence # 104170-104427, 2000 Feb; Apr. (Box 51, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence # 104430-104648, 2000 Feb. (Box 51, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence # 104650-104849, 2000 Feb; Apr. (Box 51, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence # 104850-105039, 2000 Feb; Apr. (Box 51, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence # 105040-105239, 2000 Feb; Mar. (Box 51, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence # 105240-105382, 2000 Feb; Mar. (Box 51, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence # 105390-105567, 2000 Feb; Mar. (Box 51, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence # 105570-105855, 2000 Feb; Mar. (Box 52, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence # 105860-106109, 2000 Feb; Mar. (Box 52, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence # 106110-106329, 2000 Feb; Mar; Apr. (Box 52, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence # 106330-106539, 2000 Feb; Mar; May. (Box 52, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence # 106330-106539, 2000 Feb; Mar; May. (Box 52, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence # 106730-106998, 2000 Feb; Mar; Apr; May. (Box 52, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence # 107000-107289, 2000 Mar; Apr. (Box 52, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence # 107290-107458, 2000 Mar. (Box 52, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence # 107460-107829, 2000 Mar-May. (Box 52, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence # 107830-107989, 2000 Mar-Apr. (Box 52, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence # 1107990-108118, 2000 Mar-Apr. (Box 52, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence # 108120-108323, 2000 Mar. (Box 52, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence # 108330-108564, 2000 Mar. (Box 53, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence # 108570-108649, 2000 Mar-June. (Box 53, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence # 108650-108919, 2000 Mar; Apr; May. (Box 53, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence # 108920-109159, 2000 Mar; May. (Box 53, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence # 109160-109357, 2000 Mar. (Box 53, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence # 109360-109579, 2000 Mar. (Box 53, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence # 109580-109759, 2000 Mar. (Box 53, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence # 109760-109959, 2000 Mar. (Box 53, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence # 109960-110129, 2000 Mar-Apr. (Box 53, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence # 110130-110359, 2000 Mar-Apr. (Box 53, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence # 110360-110519, 2000 Mar-Apr. (Box 53, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence # 110520-110689, 2000 Mar-Apr. (Box 54, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence # 110690-110917, 2000 Mar-Apr. (Box 54, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence # 110920-111149, 2000 Mar-Apr. (Box 54, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence # 111150-111299, 2000 Mar-Apr. (Box 54, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence # 111300-111459, 2000 Mar-Apr. (Box 54, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence # 111460-111599, 2000 Mar-Apr. (Box 54, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence # 111600-111778, 2000 Mar-Apr. (Box 54, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence # 111780-111999, 2000 Mar-Apr; June. (Box 54, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence # 112001-112169, 2000 Mar-Apr. (Box 54, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence # 112170-112339, 2000 Mar-Apr. (Box 54, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence # 112340-112478, 2000 Mar-Apr. (Box 54, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence # 112480-112629, 2000 Apr. (Box 54, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence # 112630-112779, 2000 Apr. (Box 55, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence # 112780-112939, 2000 Apr. (Box 55, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence # 112940-113099, 2000 Apr-June. (Box 55, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence # 113100-113239, 2000 Apr. (Box 55, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence # 113240-113388, 2000 Apr. (Box 55, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence # 113390-113499, 2000 Apr. (Box 55, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence # 113500-113718, 2000 Apr-May. (Box 55, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence # 113720-113979, 2000 Apr-Sept. (Box 55, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence # 113980-114219, 2000 Apr. (Box 55, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence # 114220-114375, 2000 Apr. (Box 55, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence # 114380-114656, 2000 Apr-May. (Box 55, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence # 114660-115188, 2000 Apr. (Box 55, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence # 115190-115739, 2000 Apr-May. (Box 56, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence # 115740-116057, 2000 Apr-May. (Box 56, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence # 116060-116228, 2000 Apr-May. (Box 56, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence # 200001-200189, 2000 Apr-May. (Box 56, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence # 200190-200462, 2000 May-June. (Box 56, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence # 200470-200649, 2000 Apr-May. (Box 56, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence # 200650-200859, 2000 May. (Box 56, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence # 200900-201128, 2000 May. (Box 56, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence # 201130-201349, 2000 May. (Box 56, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence # 201350-201599, 2000 May. (Box 56, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence # 201603-201839, 2000 May. (Box 56, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence # 201840-201979, 2000 May. (Box 56, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence # 201980-202217, 2000 May. (Box 56, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence # 202220-202399, 2000 May-June. (Box 57, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence # 202400-202629, 2000 May-June. (Box 57, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence # 202630-202879, 2000 May-June. (Box 57, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence # 202880-203039, 2000 May-June. (Box 57, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence # 203040-203190, 2000 May-June. (Box 57, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence # 203200-203405, 2000 May-June. (Box 57, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence # 203410-203618, 2000 May-June. (Box 57, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence # 203620-203856, 2000 May-June. (Box 57, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence # 203860-204068, 2000 May-June. (Box 57, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence # 204070-204399, 2000 May-June. (Box 57, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence # 204400-204659 2000 June. (Box 57, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence # 204660-204868, 2000 June. (Box 57, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence # 204870-205248, 2000 June. (Box 57, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence # 205250-205477, 2000 June-July. (Box 57, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence # 205480-205728, 2000 June-July. (Box 58, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence # 205730-205985, 2000 June-July. (Box 58, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence # 2002647-2004862, 2000 Apr; May; June-July. (Box 58, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence # 2004950-2006348, 2000 June. (Box 58, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence # 2006350-2006699, 2000 June. (Box 58, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence # 2006705-2007067, 2000 June-July. (Box 58, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence # 2007080-2007433, 2000 July. (Box 58, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence # 2007450-2007821, 2000 July. (Box 58, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence # 2007822-2008196, 2000 July. (Box 58, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence # 2008191-2008599, 2000 July. (Box 58, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence # 2008600-2008729, 2000 July. (Box 58, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence # 2008731-2009147, 2000 July. (Box 58, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence # 2009150-2009496, 2000 July. (Box 58, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence # 2009504-2010125, 2000 July. (Box 59, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence # 2010130-2010318, 2000 July. (Box 59, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence # 2010320-2010827, 2000 July-Aug. (Box 59, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence # 2010830-2011117, 2000 Aug. (Box 59, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence # 2011120-2011446, 2000 Aug. (Box 59, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence # 2011450-2011696, 2000 Aug. (Box 59, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence # 2011704-2012006, 2000 Aug. (Box 59, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence # 2012010-2013361, 2000 Aug. (Box 59, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence # 2013370-2013738, 2000 Aug. (Box 59, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence # 2013740-2014282, 2000 Aug. (Box 59, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence # 2014290-2015372, 2000 Aug. (Box 59, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence # 2015401-2015922, 2000 Aug. (Box 59, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence # 2015950-2016289, 2000 Aug-Sept. (Box 59, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence # 2016300-2016687, 2000 Sept. (Box 59, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence # 2016690-2017078, 2000 Sept. (Box 60, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence # 2017104-2018538, 2000 Sept. (Box 60, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence # 2018540-2019732, 2000 Sept. (Box 60, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence # 2019750-2025102, 2000 Sept. (Box 60, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence # 2025360-2026362, 2000 Sept. (Box 60, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence # 2026370-2026768, 2000 Sept. (Box 60, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence # 202026770-2027300, 2000 Sept. (Box 60, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence # 2027080-2027569, 2000 Sept-Oct. (Box 60, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence # 2027580-2027979, 2000 Oct. (Box 60, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence # 2027980-2027903, 2000 Oct. (Box 60, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence # 2027904-2028708, 2000 Oct. (Box 60, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence # 2028710-2029142, 2000 Oct. (Box 60, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence # 2029150-2029788, 2000 Oct. (Box 60, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence # 2029802-2030722, 2000 Oct. (Box 61, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence # 2030740-2031199, 2000 Oct. (Box 61, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence # 2031201-2031677, 2000 Oct. (Box 61, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence # 2031680-2032189, 2000 Oct. (Box 61, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence # 2032190-2033245, 2000 Oct-Nov. (Box 61, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence # 2033246-2033629, 2000 Nov. (Box 61, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence # 2033630-2034138, 2000 Nov. (Box 61, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence # 2034140-2034558, 2000 Nov. (Box 61, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence # 2034560-2034949, 2000 Nov. (Box 61, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence # 2035200-2035638, 2000 Nov. (Box 61, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence # 2035640-2035858, 2000 Nov. (Box 61, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence # 2035860-2036139, 2000 Nov. (Box 62, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence # 2036140-2036398, 2000 Nov. (Box 62, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence # 2036400-2036647, 2000 Nov-Dec. (Box 62, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence # 2036650-2036979, 2000 Dec. (Box 62, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence # 2036980-2037359, 2000 Dec. (Box 62, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence # 2037360-2037749, 2000 Dec. (Box 62, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence # 2037750-2038089, 2000 Dec. (Box 62, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence # 2038090-2038523, 2000 Dec. (Box 62, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence # 2038530-2038838, 2000 Dec. (Box 62, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence # 2038840-2039098, 2000 Dec. (Box 62, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence # 2039100-2039388, 2000 Dec. (Box 62, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence # 2039390-2039632, 2000 Dec. (Box 62, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence # 2039638-2040496, 2001 Jan. (Box 62, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence # 2040505-2040688, 2001 Jan. (Box 62, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence # 2040690-2040959, 2001 Jan. (Box 63, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence # 2040960-0241358, 2001 Jan. (Box 63, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence # 2041360-2041799, 2001 Jan. (Box 63, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence # 2041800-2042155, 2001 Jan. (Box 63, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence # 2042170-2042419, 2001 Jan. (Box 63, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence # 2042480-2042799, 2001 Jan. (Box 63, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence # 2042801-2043276, 2001 Jan. (Box 63, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence # 2043280-2044099, 2001 Jan. (Box 63, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence # 2044113-2044418, 2001 Jan. (Box 63, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence # 2044420-2044769, 2001 Jan. (Box 63, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence # 2044770-2045049, 2001 Jan. (Box 63, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence # 2045050-2045179, 2001 Jan. (Box 63, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence # 2045180-2045260, 2001 Jan. (Box 63, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence # 2045261-2045359, 2001 Jan. (Box 64, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence # 2045360-2045538, 2001 Jan. (Box 64, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence # 2045540-2045859, 2001 Jan. (Box 64, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence # 2045860-2046145, 2001 Jan. (Box 64, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence # 2046150-2046535, 2001 Jan. (Box 64, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence # 2046540-2047606, 2001 Jan-Feb. (Box 64, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence # 2047610-2047853, 2001 Feb. (Box 64, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence # 2047860-2048098, 2001 Feb. (Box 64, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence # 2048100-2048418, 2001 Feb. (Box 64, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence # 2048420-2048659, 2001 Feb. (Box 64, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence # 2048660-2048812, 2001 Feb. (Box 64, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence # 2048820-2049118, 2001 Feb. (Box 64, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence # 2049120-2049329, 2001 Feb. (Box 64, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence # 2049330-2050199, 2001 Feb. (Box 64, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence # 2050208-2050399, 2001 Feb. (Box 65, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence # 2050400-2050639, 2001 Feb. (Box 65, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence # 2050640-2050789, 2001 Feb. (Box 65, Folder 3)
  - Correspondence # 22050790-2051099, 2001 Feb. (Box 65, Folder 4)
  - Correspondence # 2051102-2051269, 2001 Feb. (Box 65, Folder 5)
  - Correspondence # 2051270-2051599, 2001 Feb. (Box 65, Folder 6)
  - Correspondence # 2051600-2051884, 2001 Feb-Mar. (Box 65, Folder 7)
  - Correspondence # 2051887-2052074, 2001 Feb. (Box 65, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence # 2052470-2052284, 2001 Feb. (Box 65, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence # 2052190-2052487, 2001 Feb. (Box 65, Folder 10)